

+46 762 876 674

zhuhuadan@gmail.com

https://zhuhuadan.com
https://github.com/MikoZhu
https://www.linkedin.com/in/hua
dan-zhu-802864134/

Stockholm, Sweden

## **EDUCATION**

Full-Stack Bootcamp Udemy(online) Sep 2022 - Sep 2023

Python and C# Hermods Yrkeshögskola(Sweden) Mar 2021 - Sep 2021

Master of HR Business and Management Aston University(UK) 2017 - 2018

Bachelor of Foreign Trade Jiangsu University of Technology (China) 2007 - 2011

## SOFTWARE EXPERTISE

HTML CSS/SCSS Tailwind
Javascript React Node.js Jest
Express.js MongoDB Authentication
SQL python C#
Figma Canva Photoshop
Agile Methodology

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Communication Presentation Coordination Organization

#### LANGUAGE

English Swedish(SVA 2) Chinese

# **HUADAN ZHU(MIKO)**

Front-End || Full-Stack Developer

## **ABOUT ME**

Huadan is multiple-talented: a software developer, a human resource (HR), and customer management specialist. With a master's degree and prior experience in HR and customer management, I am well-equipped with interpersonal skills, growth mindsets, and confidence to tackle new challenges. As a software developer, I love building/crafting applications, solving complex problems, and constantly exploring innovative technologies. Now, don't just take my word for it, and have fun exploring my portfolio! (https://zhuhuadan.com): -)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

O June 2023- Jan 2024 **Technigo, Sweden** Web Developer

Completed a rigorous 22-week coding boot camp, dedicated over 2,000 hours for coding. Gained proficiency in JavaScript (ES 6), React, HTML5, CSS, server-side programming with Node.js, MongoDB, and authentication mechanisms. Completed over 24 projects covering everything from the basics of programming to structuring web projects using the latest technology.

O Dec 2020 - Sep 2021

## SHEIN, Sweden Client Service

At SHEIN, a fast fashion company, I achieved a 98% customer satisfaction rate. Proficient in CSM, I managed 60+ daily tickets with 99% accuracy, emphasizing seamless Swedish customer experiences in logistics and returns.

Sep 2017 - Sep 2019

## UCNEST, London

Marketing and Recruiter

At a startup tech company, I recruited and trained over 30 professionals, catalyzing organizational growth. In the realm of Marketing & Customer Service, I achieved 100% sales success with a 10% contribution from customer service while expanding into the Chinese market through trend-savvy, multichannel strategies.

O Aug 2014 - Oct 2016

## World International English, China Regional HR Manager

Screened over 100 candidates and conducted 20 phone interviews daily, resulting in the recruitment of 500+ professionals, including key leaders. Orchestrated coaching programs to foster growth and aligned HR with strategic management to achieve business goals.

Feb 2013 - Jun 2014

#### SRE Group, China

## HR Supervisor

Managed HR across multiple locations, overseeing monthly interviews for 150+ candidates and achieving annual onboarding exceeding 100. Implemented competitive reward and payroll strategy, executed organization-wide HR functions, integrating KPIs, 360 assessments, SMART goals, and a performance management system.